Office of the President Jill Ker Conway Files, 1974-1985
Smith College Archives
- SERIES IX. COMMITTEES AND BOARDS
  - Early Retirement Program Study Group 1976-1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Educational Policy, Ctte on (Box 5)
    See Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Academic Policy, Ctte on
  - Election Ballots, Committee on 1977-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Electronic Equipment Study Group 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Enrollment Management Committee 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Facilities Planning Committee 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on Jan-Sep 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on Oct-Dec 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Compensation and Development, Committee on 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Compensation and Development, Committee on 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Elections, Ad-hoc Committee on 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Faculty House Advisors Committee 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Offices, Committee on 1977-1985, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Financial Aid, Committee on
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - -General 1977-1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Financial Aid [Policy] Advisory Committee 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Financial Aid Management Task Force 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid Review Committee 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Food Resources Committee 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Students, Committee on
    See also Series V. Admin. Offices -Foreign Students Office -and- Series XV. Non-Smith Orgs-Institute of International Education -and- Series XV. Non-Smith Orgs-Institute of World Affairs
    - -Annual Reports 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - -General 1976-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Freedom of Expression, Ad-hoc Committee on 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Governance for the School for Social Work, Ad Hod Committee on (Box 7)
    See Series XIII. Graduate Work-School for Social Work-Ad Hoc Committee on Governance
  - Graduate Study, Committee on 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Grievance, Committee on 1975-1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    See also Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Administrative Staff Grievance Ctte -and- Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Clerical Staff Grievance Ctte -and- Intra-College Disputes, Ad Hoc Ctte on
  - Grounds Committee 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Honorary Degrees, Committee on 1978-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Honors and Independent Programs, Committee on 1975-1982, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Interterm Committee 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Interterm Committee 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Interterm Committee 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Interterm Committee 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Interterm Committee 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Intra-College Disputes, Ad-hoc Committee on 1975-1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Jahnige Center Advisory Committee 1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Lectures, Committee on 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Library Committee 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Luce Scholarship Selection Committee 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Marshalls Committee 1977-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Medieval Studies Council 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Motion Pictures, Committee on 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Non-Print Resource Center Committee 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Parents Committee (Box 8)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Parents Ctte
  - Personnel Policy Board 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Physical Education, Ad-hoc Committee on 1980-81 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Planning & Resources, Committee on (Box 8)
    See Series IX. Committees & Boards-College Planning & Resources Committee
  - Pre-Major Advisors, Board of 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Pre-Medical Advisors, Board of 1977-1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - President's Office/Board of Trustees, Ad-hoc Committee to Evaluate the Functions of 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - President's Committee (Box 8)
    See Series V. Admin. Offices-Development-President's Ctte
  - Presidential Search Committee 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Quality of Life Management Group
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - -Final Report 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Radiation Safety Committee 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Recruitment and Retention of Minority Faculty, Ad-hoc Ctte to Study the 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Recruitment and Retention of Women Faculty, Ad-hoc Ctte to Study the 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Registration of Students, Committee on 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Rental Properties, Advisory Committee on 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Research Program on Women, Ad-hoc Committee to Design a 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Resource Development Committee (Box 8)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Development- Resource Development Committee
  - Science Advisory Committee 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Science Committee on Long-Range Planning 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Science Planning Committee 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Senior Administrative Group 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Senior Staff 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Senior Staff Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Senior Staff Jul-Dec 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Senior Staff Jan-Aug 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Senior Staff Sep-Dec 1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Senior Staff Jan-May 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Senior Staff Jun-Dec 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Senior Staff 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Senior Staff 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Senior Staff 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Smith College Medal Committee 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Social Responsibility, Committee on 1975-1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Social Responsibility, Committee on 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Space Allocation, Committee on 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Staff Development Association (Box 10)
    See Series IX. Committees & Boards-Administrative and Clerical Personnel Advisory Boards
  - Status of Women and Men, Committee on the 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Student Affairs, Committee on
    - -General 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - -General Jan-Jul 1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - -General Aug-Dec 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - -General 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - -General 1978-1983, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - -March 1976 Disturbance in Wright Hall 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Study Abroad, Committee on 1976-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Teacher Education, Advisory Committee on 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tenure, Ad-hoc Study Group on 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Tenure and Promotion, Committee on 1975-1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Term-Line Internships, Committee on 1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Twelve-College Selection Committee 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Use of Human Subjects in Research, Committee on 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Word Processing Committee 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- SERIES X. ENGAGEMENTS
  This series of records works in concert with the Speeches and Events series to provide a detailed description of the activities and responsibilities of the President of Smith College. Included are a set of files containing details of various off-campus appointments and events the president attended (organized by date of event or appointment). There are also a set of calendars, daily schedules, travel schedules, and a sample of engagements the president had to refuse.
  - August-December 1975 ca. 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - January-March 1976 ca. 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - April 1976 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - May-July 1976 ca. 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - September-October 1976 ca. 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - November 1976 ca. 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - December 1976 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - January-February 1977 ca. 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - March-June 1977 ca. 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - September-December 1977 ca. 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - January-June 1978 ca. 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - September-October 1978 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - February 1979 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - May-June 1979 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - September 1979-Olin Fellows Program 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - September 1979-Wellesley College, Research Conference & #8230; 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - October 1979 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - January-April 1980 ca. 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - June 1980 ca. 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - November 1980 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - February-May 1981 ca. 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - June 1981 ca. 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - September-October 1981 ca. 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - January-May 1982 ca. 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - June 1982 ca. 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - September-November 1982 ca. 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - May-August 1983 ca. 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - April 1984 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - May 1984-Westover School 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - June 1984-Cathedral School of St. Mary's 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - September 1984-University of Maine 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - September 1984-Mt Holyoke Symposium on Women's Higher Education 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - October 1984 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - October 1984-Cambridge Forum 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - October 1984-Queen's University 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - November 1984-University of Toronto 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - May 1985-Women's National Democratic Club 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - June 1985-Webb School Commencement 1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Calendars
    - -1976 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - -1977 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - -1978 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - -1979 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -1980 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -1981 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -1982 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -1983 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -1984 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -1985 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Daily Schedules
    - -1977-1979 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - -1980 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -Jan-May 1981 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - -Jun-Sep 1981 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Oct-Dec 1981 1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -Jan-Mar 1982 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -Apr-Jun 1982 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -Jul-Sep 1982 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - -Oct-Dec 1982 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -Jan-Mar 1983 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -Apr-Jun 1983 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -Jul-Sep 1983 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - -Oct-Dec 1983 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - -Jan-Mar 1984 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - -Apr-Jun 1984 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - -Jul-Sep 1984 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Oct-Dec 1984 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -Jan-Mar 1985 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -Apr-Jun 1985 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Travel Schedules 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Travel Schedules 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Refusals 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Refusals 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Refusals 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- SERIES XI. EVENTS
  Along with the Speeches and Engagements series, the records in this series document the activities and responsibilities of the President of Smith College. The events in this series (as opposed to the Engagements series) include significant campus traditional gatherings and celebrations as well as one-time happenings. Routine events include assemblies, commencement, Rally Day, and the awarding of Smith College Medals and honorary degrees. Other events include Conway's inauguration, concerts, conferences, symposia, lectures, as well as various events at the President's House.
  Material on the Jeane Kirkpatrick debacle can also be found in this series with the records of the 1983 commencement.
  - Centennial-Centennial Film 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Vespers 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Commencement (Box 1)
    See also Series VI. Alumnae-Reunions -and- Series IX. Cttes & Bds -Commencement Wknd, Ctte on -and- Series XI. Events-Honorary Degrees
  - Commencement- 1976
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -Name Reading Petition 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -Speaker 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Commencement- 1977
    - -General 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -President's Luncheon 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -Speaker 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Thomas C. Mendenhall 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Commencement- 1978
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -Speaker 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Commencement- 1979
    - -General 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -Speaker 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Commencement- 1980
    - -General 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - -Luncheon 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - -Speaker 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Commencement- 1981
    - -General 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - -Luncheon 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - -Speaker 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commencement- 1982
    - -General 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Baldwin House Complaints 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -Rain Relocation 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -Speaker 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commencement- 1983
    - -General 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Speaker
      - -General 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - -Jeane Kirkpatrick
        - -Correspondence
          - -General 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
          - -Kirkpatrick 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - -Alumnae
            - -General 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
            - -A-B ca. 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
            - -C-E ca. 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
            - -F-H ca. 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
            - -I-L ca. 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
            - -M-O ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
            - -P-R ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
            - -S-T ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
            - -U-Z ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
          - -Ctte on Social Responsibility 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - -Faculty 1983-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
          - -Parents, A-Z ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
          - -Students 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
          - -Other
            - -A-C ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
            - -D-F ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
            - -G-J ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
            - -K-O ca. 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
            - -P-R ca. 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
            - -S-Z ca. 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - -Press
          - -Clippings 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
          - -Clippings undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
          - -Releases/Responses 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - - 1984
      - -General 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - -Speaker 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - - 1985
      - -General 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - -Speaker 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Concerts
    - -General 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - -Ernst Wallfisch Memorial Fund Concerts 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Conferences
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Conference Committee
    - -General 1978-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - -Berkshire Conference of Women Historians 1977-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - -Bridge to the Eighties (Box 4)
      See Administrative Offices-Development-Bridge to the Eighties Conference
    - -Capitalism and Socialism, Proposed 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - -[Ruth] Draper Centennial Celebration 1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - -Energy and the Environment 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Ethics in Medicine and Science 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -History of Women's Higher Education 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -International Women's Year 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -Latin American Women Writers 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -Margaret Sanger Centennial Conference 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -Music in Paris in the 1830s 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -The Older Undergraduate Woman
      - -General 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - -Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Report 1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - -Radcliffe Report 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - -Transcript 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - -Preserving Women's History: Archivists and Historians… 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - -Protective Legislation and Women's Employment 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - -Shaping Space: An Interdisciplinary Conference on Polyhedra 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - -Shargo Memorial Conference: Working With Refugees 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - -Women and Sport, Proposed 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - -Women in Science 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - -Women, Welfare & Public Policy (Box 6)
      See Series V. Admin. Offices-Development-Fdns-Commonwealth Fund, Mott Fdn, and Rockefeller Fdn
  - Conway Celebration Day 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Degrees 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    See also: Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Honorary Degrees, Ctte on -and- Series XI. Events-Commencement -and- Series XI. Events-Rally Day -and- Series XI. Events-Commencement-1983-Speaker-J. Kirkpatrick
  - Inauguration
    - -Program 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -Inaugural Address
      - -Final Copy 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - -Drafts 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - -Requests for Copies 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -Publicity 1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -Speakers 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -Accompanying Events
      - -Ecumenical Service 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - -Luncheon 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - -Music 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - -Reception & Dinner 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - -Invitations 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - -Guest Lists 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - -Replies 1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
        - -Acceptance Cards, A-J 1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
        - -Acceptance Cards, K-Z 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
        - -Regrets Cards 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - -Congratulations 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - -Thank You Notes
      - -General 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - -Staff 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - -Planning
      - -Correspondence 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - -Inaugural Committee Minutes 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - -Budget 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - -Arrangements for Guests 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - -Academic Procession 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Interterm 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Interterm Committee
  - Interterm 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Interterm 1980-1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Lectures & Visiting Scholars
    - -General 1975-1985, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - -Margaret Atwood (Box 7)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Libraries-Renovation Dedication
    - -Begin, Monique 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - -Barnabas, Manorama 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - -Bell, Diane 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - -Bridges to Pluralism 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - -Bush, Barbara (Box 7)
      See Series VI. Alumnae-Individuals-Bush, Barbara
    - -Chan-Palay, Victoria 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - -Clark, Manning 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - -Collins, Cherry 1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - -Dalai Lama 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - -[Katharine Asher] Engel Lecture 1976-1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - -Fuente, Beatriz de la 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - -Galiulin, Ravil 1980 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - -Hotchkiss, Joan 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - -Im, Wha Kong 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - -Rodrigues, Sister Livi 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - -Smith, Gerard 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - -[An Evening With Gloria] Steinem and Jill Ker Conway 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - -Women in Science Series 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - -Woodrow Wilson National Foundation Visiting Fellows 1975, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - -Yates, Frances 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Mountain Day 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Opening Convocation 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Parent's Weekend 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - President's House Events (Box 8)
    See also Series VII. Bldgs & Grounds-President's Hse
    - -General 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - -General 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - -General 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - -General 1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - -General 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - -General 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - -General 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - -General 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - -General 1985, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - -College Hall Christmas Party 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - -Freshman Reception 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - -Gold Key Receptions 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - -New Faculty Reception 1976-1985, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -Senior Dinners 1976-1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rally Day
    - -1976 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - -1977 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - -1978 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - -1979 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - -1980 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - -1981 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - -1982 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - -1983 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - -1984 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - -1985 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Smith College Medals (Box 10)
    See Series XI. Events-Rally Day -and- Series IX. Committees & Boards-Smith College Medal Committee
  - Summer Programs 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Summer Programs 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Symposia
    - -General 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - -[Ely] Chinoy Memorial Symposia 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - -Diaghilev Symposium 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - -Martin Luther Symposium 1984 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - -New Labor History and the New England Working Class 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - -New Labor History and the New England Working Class 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - -New Labor History and the New England Working Class 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - -[Dorothy] Wrinch Symposium: Structures of Matter… 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- SERIES XII. FACULTY AND STAFF
  The records in this series document the relationship of the President's Office with faculty and staff. There is information on a number of general faculty and staff issues, such as salaries and retirement, as well as information about specific individuals. Material relating to emeritus faculty and staff (including former Smith presidents and their families) can be found in this series as well.
  Additional material for specific faculty or staff members may be found in the Academic Departments, Administrative Offices, or Committees and Boards series. The Committees and Boards series also includes records for a number of faculty and staff-related committees. The records of the Women and Social Change Project, a faculty-research endeavor, is also included in this series. There is general administrative material for the project as well as a number of grant applications.
  - General 1975-1984, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Black Faculty and Administrators 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Emeritus Presidents & Their Families
    - -Mendenhall 1975-1977, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -Wright 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Endowed Professorships
    - -General 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -Kennedy Professors 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Neilson Professors 1975-1984, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Club 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Club 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Club 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Exchange With the University of Hamburg 1976-1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Exchange With the University of Sussex 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Luncheons 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Salaries
    - -General 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)